She has a Balenciaga bag.  It
matches the dress.  Your friend will drive today.
You have become a heroine.
Darling, I told you.  Your
friend is coming from Chandigarh.  She is saying that you went out
alone for a walk.  She did not take me.
Catch hold hold.   Let's have
fun.  Like making fun of a man for fun.
[MUSIC]
Good morning guys.  Welcome back to another
vlog.  So brother, today's vlog is going to be very interesting.  First of all,
I am going to introduce you to Tuba.
And our Tuba Rani,
brother, looks like a
girl from Goa, so the dress she is wearing is
amazing.  And most
importantly, the color she wore is my favorite
color.  What's the matter, what's the matter.  So now
we are going to visit Goa.   I have to
go in a car or on a scooter.  Tell quickly.
Tuba will roam around in a scooter.  Ok.  So brother,
Tuba is looking very beautiful and cute, my
baby doll.  Tuba, my glasses have disappeared, friend.  Ca
n't find it.  What should I do,
Tuba?  You are wearing
this pair of glasses, friend. Otherwise, the other one has
disappeared. You know, the
white one.
Yes, I am not able to find the white one. So, brother, one of my
glasses has disappeared. I mean, wear this one
above. I had worn it at the party, I don't know, I
forgot to keep it there. I am not able to find it at home. Or have I not
forgotten? I am not able to find Tuba.
What should I do? Forget it
there, for sure.
Brother, if you have met Tuba, then
meet Payal as well. Brother, Payal has dressed
up like this today. And after that, you will
go around Goa on a scooter. So, brother, Payal has just
surprised me.  You also meet me
once and touch wood, meaning Payal should not be affected by evil eye.
I feel like brother,
how can she look so young?  Come brother Payal.  Well,
Chiku has hidden the anklet.
Yes sir.
Oho oh ho oh ho what's the matter Payal.  You have been
creating terror, my friend.  Look, just like
our little doll, Payal is
looking so big.
Why?
Yes sir.  She looks like mom, she looks like sister.
Mom, you are looking like a sister, so please do
my shopping today.   He is
saying that you look like my sister.
Yes sir.  Let's go then,
Papa.   Let's go.   Let's
go on the scooter.
Daughter, you also get ready.  I have to go on a scooter.   I do.
Ok.  Tuba, what is this in your hand,
son?   There
is a surprise for mom.
Payal, I have a surprise for you.  What a surprise,
son?
You should look at his bag first.  She has a Balenciaga
bag.
Good.   It
matches the dress.
Okay, show it again.
Payal, don't go to any club inside this and
take this bag with you.  Take it from this bag,
today it
is there for
us to see the mirror in it,
okay sir, this is Tuba's bag,
yes sir, let's do
one thing, let's open Payal's bag today and
see what all is there in Payal's bag,
okay, I will
show you,
brother, today it will be live, Payal's bag,
what's in my bag, this is
my new bag, guys, today I have bought it
for me and Golu, so brother, if we
open it, first of all there is a wallet in my purse, there is some cash,
after that there is a towel because the kids are going with us to the
beach, after that there is a diaper for my
Tuba.  Then there's Vice for my tuba.
Ok.
After that, all the women have it.
After that a perfume for Armaan ji.
Then a clip and then a
box of goggles because I had already changed one yesterday.
So I thought if they take it out,
I will put it in this.  And one is
sunscreen.  That's it.   Did
you see it, wow?  Look, do you know how much stuff mom is
taking with her?   I
also have my stuff.
Good.   Please
check it.  It is for mom.
Guddu is for me.  Look, there is a liner, there
is a mirror, then she picked up some
glass lids from here, then this toy which she
bought yesterday,
okay, then there is a tissue paper which is used,
okay, after that there
is a stone also,
oh oh Gudu, if someone teases her, then
look, she has kept this, it is
kept to hit her, okay,
girls keep paper spray, that's why she
keeps stones, then she has a Bhole ji
bracelet, then she has a card, then she has this
one with the alphabet of your name,
right, right, Tuba, brother, Payal
hung her bags and Payal is saying,
I will drive the scooter, Payal, okay,
your friend will drive the scooter today, okay,
where are we going, by the way, Payal, we will
sit on the side of some beach, we will sing two songs of love, we have given our
heart, come on,
then brother, I have just come out
and we have four scooters, four, so let's
see which
scooter Payal will use when she comes out, so I feel like
Payal will either like this pink one, this one,
this one, or that one.  That one, that one
can also come, it
can come, brother,
and brother, here in Goa, there is no way to know about the weather, one
cannot know when it will rain.  So we're going to
take a camera.  Even if it rains,
we will keep it inside the trunk.  Okay, right
?  And brother, this villa is awesome,
I mean, whenever you come to Goa, you will
definitely feel like home here.   It will be a
good experience.   Isn't it
?
Very good.
So Payal, neither before starting the vlog
nor before I had told her that these are scooters
and let's see which scooter Payal will like.
So which scooter did Payal drive?
Tell me quickly.  This
Shagun had also said the same thing.  Yes yes
I said Payal also likes that colour.
Yes, that too Tuba but black
Tuba, son, leave this bag here, son.
What's in it?
Do one thing Tuba, put your bag in my bag.
Yes, give it to mom.
Chiku, you know how to drive a scooter.
Yes, Papa, I get it a little bit.
Son, that one is the other one with battery.  He will
not be able to drive this scooter.
Okay, fine, dad.
No problem.  I will try to
teach you.  Ok.
[Music]
So guys, we just stopped here and brother, there is
such a beautiful beach, there is Paharwad too.  Chiku, do
you want to catch fish?
Yes sir.
I do one thing, I
call a fisherman and make Chiku do the fishing.
Ok?  Ok?
And you like watching fish very much.
Oh brother, look at the scene in front, Payal.
How much?
This is a little bit of sunshine.  But you are enjoying it,
right Chiku?
Yes, Baba is my father.
Payal, this time we had a lot of fun
in Goa.  Yes and we still have time till tomorrow evening.
What will you do next time?  We will come with the whole family for
15 days.  Is it okay son?
Payal, let's make half a video of both of us.
Yes darling.   Isn't it
?  I am wearing Payal's clothes like this.
Darling, I told you, my friend
darling.
You have become a heroine.
Darling, I told you.   Okay, no
problem.  Let's take a slomo
there.
Okay darling.
Tuba you want to go fishing?
Yes sir.  Come on, show me your hands.  I told you not to
put your hands in the mud.  I told you, okay
papa, tell me.
Friend, please explain this to him a little.
Your hand will get infected.  Don't do it
[music]
Payal come back.  Tuba [screaming]
Come to me.  Come running.  Fast fast
Tuba.  Very good very good so brother right now
people are fishing there
so let's go and see Tuba see the fish, let's
go and see the fishing okay
dad there is food too
see
who eats fish when did you eat baba I will eat it
now you will eat it
now you will not eat it raw
and I will
cook it and eat it after
catching it [laughs] come on then
Payal in the lap of the sea there are such
stones in it
look how many big stones are there here
big ones okay for jumping sail look how many are there to jump
yes on the shore oh I have gone to the corals when
we came to Goa earlier there are
stones like this below there are a lot of moss on them
yes let's go then brother just now we
wanted to go there but that brother
he said that brother you cannot go there
because only the local people can go right now there are
small children the water
waves come up very quickly and they have experience
we don't have
we have that right it's okay let's go back
brother just now Tuba's one  I am getting a call
from Chandigarh, who is coming outside,
Tuba's friend is coming from Chandigarh, she is saying that
you went out alone for a walk.  She did not take me.
Tuba, you have to drink Waterman juice now.
Ok.  So right now we're going brother up and we're
tired of drinking juice.  And
our Chiku is playing there and
Ujjwal is with him to take care of him.  So brother, don't
come from home.  I feel like she has
brought the fan remote.  He has the fan remote and
hair in his hand.  Isn't it?
[Music] So brother, our Cheeku is tired.
And brother, the view from here
looks so amazing, doesn't it?  Now,
if we go inside and eat something and then look around,
Chiku is looking good now, right?
Yes Baba, it feels good Baba, let me play volleyball.   Let's
play volleyball.
Yes, play?
Call him.  Yes Payal, let's play volleyball.
So brother, the requirement of Payal is increasing.
Yes brother Pal ji, tell me.
Friend Guddu, today is our last night in Goa.
So I am thinking that you should take me out somewhere tonight also.
Okay, then I will take Chiku along with me.
okay brother.
We will drop Tuba home.  Okay daughter.
Tuba wants to stay home?
No.
Why?
I also have to go.   Don't talk nonsense.
Okay, right?  You misbehaved last night too,
son, I am removing your hands. You are biting your nails. You are
not biting your nails. It is her hand. That's not how you do it.
Okay, not her hand. Okay,
why do you want to go, brother, you tell me,
why do you want to go?
How will I go?
Children have nothing to do
there. Then you climb on my lap.
Yes, a lot of people come, you
dance, you do something, you climb on my lap there.
Then you trouble
our mind.
Yes, I will go to the
club there,
stay at home. Okay, Tuba, you have to
catch Papa. Okay, come,
Tuba, come quickly. [laughs] Catch, catch, catch, catch. Come, come, run quickly. [laughs
] Run quickly. Catch, catch. [laughs]
Dust Baba,
Baba,
yes son
[laughs]
Come, come, come. Don't run.
Why don't I run? Catch [laughs]
Come
[laughs]
Oh my daughter, my daughter, it's
good that I have caught her.
I am tired. Let's go, you are my life.
Whose life are you?
Come, I am tired. Brother, Payal is saying that I am on the
scooter.  I will ride the
scooter, I will ride it and after going home I will take a bath in flowers. Come on
brother, after going home I will make Payal
play a game and I will make my sister play a game. It is
absolutely fine.
Whoever wins, we will take him to the party at night,
otherwise we will not take him. It is done,
okay I will make him play
one game after going home. Okay,
Tuba, show me your duck.  What are
you sitting on?   On
the duck.
Who brought it for you?
Mama.
Brother, your mother has given you a surprise,
Tuba.   Are you
enjoying it?
Mummy, Chiku Dada told you.
Chiku Dada made them wet.  Chiku Dada son is like this.
What to do?  Isn't it?  Look up here.  Are you
enjoying it?
Papa, Mummy.   Should
I take you out?   Must come
?
Yes.
Just took a bath?
So brother, Tuba has kept her legs out while sitting inside it.
And I had brought this anklet for him in the
afternoon.  Cheeku
brother, Cheeku, it's the third time he's gone into the water, it's the
third time this boy brother is enjoying so much,
these two kids are
very fond of water, they go crazy as soon as they see water, they get
wet, should I take you out
[screaming sound], they're having a
lot of fun,
okay I'll take you out, wait
brother, Payal is ready, Payal is saying,
brother, today I'm going to take a bath, very good, Payal,
you have to swim sideways, okay, I don't know how to
swim sideways, look, I
can't swim on my own, I'll go down slowly,
with the child, protect his hands, he has
tape, you apply tape, he does
n't have
tape,
but I'll take care of him myself,
okay
[music]
so brother, we'll take full care of Topa, his
death has come, today I thought that before we go,
why not enjoy the swimming pool, we've already enjoyed
some man by making fun of him,
we'll enjoy the swimming pool by taking a
bath [laughs] by
swimming like a fish, but you take care of yourself
now, but remember,
you take care of yourself  She had come.  I
brought mine.  [Music]
So brother, you just came and I cleaned my hands
and I'm applying medicine.  One of
your hands is completely fine, right?  This
hand is completely fine.  Apply this.  Can
do everything from tomorrow.  That hand will be fine in a day or two.
Ok.  Friend Tuba, you did it
yourself.  I tell you so many times
that Tuba, stop.  Tuba stop.
I do.  Wait, I will do it.  Hello
kids, how are you?  [screaming sound] Hello
Dada,
how are you? Zada, I have to bring the
kids to Chungri.
Okay, Tuba Rani is speaking. Show me here. Did you
ask what you want? What do you want?
Tell me what you want.
Yes,
donkey, golden donkey,
son, that is at home.
What do you want?
I do
n't eat candy with water. Okay, I don't eat candy. It's a dirty thing.
Tell me, I'll bring
candy. I'll bring it. Let me
eat it. No problem.
Brother, I did some shopping today
for you. I know there are a lot of network
issues. So,
Papa is shopping.
oh,
yes son,
come here, I'll call you for a minute. Come here,
son. Here is Guddu.
Okay, Krishna, tell me, first of all, this
vlogging that you're doing. Who is dubbing it? Here is
Zada ​​and Ranu. Are you
both doing it together? Do you do it one line at a time?
Very good, very good. Zada, I am missing
Papa.
Yes, Papa, I am here. I came
yesterday. Okay,
I am having fun. No
problem. You can play. Okay, okay,
tell me, play brother. Okay,
play brother.  I will
also make laddus of ragi,
for whom have I made these, Golu, you have
made these for the children, I have myself
made dal laddus, today or tomorrow I will
make ragi laddus, so keep them on the dining table, you will
come and eat one laddu, you will get everything in it, there is
no sugar in it, it is
fine, it is fine, we will eat it after coming, we are
near, you say mummy, I will eat it, mummy,
I will eat it from aunty.
Yes, why not, I have kept a lot of them
safely for you, son.
Mom aunty, please come carefully.
Son aunty, he has not come yet, he is
stuck in traffic.  It is not raining here.   I don't have
anyone stuck in peace traffic.
I will go alone,
okay Golu, take care.  Ok.
Ok?
You are not Naina Naina, sister-in-law.
Naina is with Rudra.  Just
with Rudra today.  Tell them I am coming.  Just
say it.
I am just coming.
Payal calls him and says Pachiku
is in the water for the last one hour.  He is not improving.   Put
him to sleep on time and put this one to sleep too.
Put both of them to sleep.
Yes, put both of them to sleep on time.  Okay
Tuba.  You are not going anywhere with me today.
Ok.  Ok.
You are at home today.  Ok.
Why dad?
Son, children do not go there.  Children are not allowed.
Wherever we are going, we give
injections to the children as soon as we enter.
I will not go.
No.  Ok.
when will you come?  Father.
I will come.  I will come in a while.  I will just put
you to sleep and leave.
We
are fine.
I,
Chiku Bhai, am also with you.  Ok.
Father.
Yes.  Then I am also a grandfather.
Why?
Chiku Dada will go with you.
Chiku Dada is also with you.  Aunty ji is also there.  Is
n't he here?  Everything is there.  Sister is also everything.
What are you saying?   I will put you to sleep around
8-8:30.  We'll
play downstairs for a while.
Ok.
Come.
Come, come, I am here.  Easy Easy Very
Good.  Papa is waiting right now.
Come slowly.  Don't be hasty.  Well done.  Come on.
Chiku, it's been an hour since you took bath.   Come out.  Will fall
ill.  Son, you also
come out.  Let us go.  Come out, children.  Come here my
love.  Come, should I catch you?  Should I hold your hand?  Come on.
Walk slowly, slowly, slowly, carefully, carefully
brother,
I liked this stone of the stairs so much, I mean walk after getting it wet, let's
do it like this,
see, no matter how rough and tough you make it, it does
n't matter brother, it is
very fun brother,
so guys, let me give you a tour of this entire village
and that too we
shot everything inside and outside with a drone, I mean you will be
interested, you will enjoy watching it and if
someone wants to make such a design for his house, it will be
useful for him too, then brother check it out
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
So brother, right now we are going to a party
and here brother Chiku's breath has dried up.
Yesterday he was wearing one of my glasses and
I took that from him.  I
think it is not his fault.
I had worn those glasses there and after that I am
not able to find those glasses.  Maybe you stayed in the car
or 90% as far as I can think.
I
100% get your glasses at the same restaurant.
I forgot myself on the table.  Chiku said on the table.
I had it all.  It's not your fault.   Don't
worry.  What happened?  I was scared.   I was
so scared.   Don't
scare me.  No problem.  And we will take more.
What happened?   Make me
sleep with you.
Ok.  No, he is there, Anuj, isn't he?  Anuj
is with him,
Papa, he's editing. Right now, it's okay.
You see, tomorrow, not today. You
woke up very early. What's your work?
You'll fall asleep as soon as you go. He's been swimming outside for two hours. What's more, he's been
swimming for two hours. So, quickly go
upstairs and sleep in a minute. Okay,
okay, Papa, I'll eat and put him to sleep.
Brother, here my daughter Tuba is all ready.
Tuba is saying, "
Papa, wherever you go, I'll go. You'll come
with me." Okay, you won't cry. Now,
show me your hands for sure. Quickly, show me your hands.
My daughter's hands. Brother, wash your hands a little. They're
healing. It'll take some time, won't
you? But no, the daughter is stung. Papa
's stung.
Papa, it's hurting here. No
problem. Then do one thing. Stay home. Do
n't go stay with Chiku. Tell me quickly. Don't mess with me. Do
n't mess with me.
Okay, I mean, you want to come with Payal.
Convince her once, friend. I want her to
play here with the kids. Tuba, do one thing, son. You should let the
kids go.  Stay here with her,
yes enjoy with the kids, I know
why, let me tell you, these
kids have not slept and she has woken up from sleep.
Okay,
we have to
go together,
yes, I have
finally decided,
yes,
Chiku Bhai, see, I am explaining to you very lovingly,
if I do
n't find you on your bed within 20 minutes, then I will have to come back,
okay, I will leave it,
brother, here our car is
completely ready and our sister is also
ready and here Harsh Bhai is saying,
I will drive the car, Harsh Bhaiya, come on, then
your brother will drive the car,
how long have you slept for
an hour,
okay, I saw the entire vlog, when we were
not picking up the drone, when the drone had fallen down, the
glasses and the drone were kept on the table, this benefit of the vlog remained
there
and I told him that now I will
see.  I don't watch it.  I
saw the same glasses in Vogue, they are kept on the table.   Something similar happened
once, we were just shooting.
Someone stole my phone from the shoot
and I wasn't blogging like this.
Hello guys, it is not visible who is picking it up.
[laughs]
So, brother, we were all ready and everyone was
sitting in the back.  There is Shagun and Ujjwal
and we have left Anuj at home with Chiku
because brother Chiku does not trust us.
He can jump into the swimming pool even at night.  So right now we are going to Nova Cafe, isn't it
brother? Yes,
Nova Cafe, that is the
best thing here, it is
number one right now, it is trending in Anjana
Baga area.
I will make a vlog about it so that you people
know what is going on in the society,
who is taking care of their children, their wife, their family, so do
not comment on it at all, brother, people are drinking alcohol,
things happen everywhere,
my only aim is to show you, so
brother, here Tuba wants to say something,
Tuba, do you want to say something, son, what should I say?
Coco asked, is grandmother at home?
Yes, Coco asked, son, she is your elder sister.
He is 13 years old.
I am 10 years older than you.
Yes,
my mother-in-law has dogs at her house, they are
13 year old dogs.
Well
her name is Coco Puchi.
He had become so ill in between, yet
he takes so much care of me.
One of them had skin cancer.
Yes.
Oh
dog Coco.  Meaning I love you very much.
He is a very big dog lover.
Good sir.
One.
So guys finally Bhaiya we have reached
Tuba.  Son, we have come next.  Enjoy enjoy enjoy enjoy
so brother you are having a great time in Goa
yes son
I was sleeping will you give me fever
son if you don't sleep then all of you get ready
quickly in a minute
brother come on ahead where is that one brother do you have to
get down very fast
oh brother I am telling you so I will get down right now
brother we are going I feel as if there were
no lanes in foreign countries come on come on
Tuba Shagun brother pick up Tuba
tell me when have you been abroad
brother friend was born in a foreign country oh ho which one did you
say that
brother you are looking very beautiful friend friend
I always keep myself beautiful
you are looking more beautiful today bye
yes
thank you I
mean dress up like this I told you earlier
also to dress up
you have told me but there is no one I get stuck in the household chores
now don't get stuck go out every month okay so
brother we have finally reached Nova Club and this is the
most famous club of Goa guys
so guys today  Vogue we end here.
hello.  Bye-bye.